Guide to the William A. Tuttle Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
William A. Tuttle family papers
1800-1937
MS 511
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.5
(5 boxes)
The papers consist of correspondence, volumes, albums, legal and financial papers, and photographs relating to the Tuttle family of Connecticut.
Tuttle, William A.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Charles G. Morris, 1943.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The papers consist of correspondence, volumes, albums, legal and financial papers, and photographs relating to the Tuttle family of Connecticut.
Families; Connecticut; New Haven (Conn.) -- Description and travel -- Views; Orange (Conn.) -- Politics and government; West Haven (Conn.) -- Politics and government; Autographs; Photoprints; Public officers; Tuttle, Louis E.; Tuttle, Lucius Bement; Tuttle, Sarah L. Bement; Tuttle, William A.; Tuttle family; Yale University -- Description and travel -- Views
- Inventory
  - Legal and financial papers, 1800-1812, 1840-1890, 1930, nd (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1842-1937 (Box 1)
  - Political papers of William A. Tuttle, including 28 notices informing him of election to public offices in West Haven and Orange, Conn., 1896-1919 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Union Cards, 1881-1882 (Box 1)
    - Cloth sack, undated (Box 1)
  - Bound Volumes
    - Louis E. Tuttle: scrapbook, with additions by William A. Tuttle, 1869-1924 (Box 1)
    - Lucius Bement Tuttle: circulars, rules re paymaster of the navy, 1864-1865 (Box 1)
    - Sarah L. (Bement) Tuttle (Mrs. Edward H.): autograph album, 1840-1855 (Box 1)
    - William A. Tuttle
      - Autograph album, 1882-1893 (Box 1)
      - Registers of voters. Bourough of West Haven. Town of Orange.
        - 1901-1902 (Box 1)
        - 1902-1909 (Box 2)
        - 1910-1916 (Box 3)
        - 1918-1920, n.d. (Box 4)
      - Tuttle family: photograph album, undated (Box 4)
  - Oversize
    - William A. Tuttle: 2 albums of photographs of Yale and New Haven, and other places in Connecticut, with a partial index, Circa 1884-1901 (Box 5)